华盛顿特区维拉德酒店
感恩节前一天
上午 9:00
时间到了
It's time.
白宫玫瑰园
上午 10:03
一直以来感恩节意味着
Thanksgiving has always meant sharing the bounty
享用这片沃土给我们的奖赏
of our rich land,
尤其是火鸡
especially turkey.
不过今年的感恩节上我们不会分享的
But the one thing we will not be sharing this holiday
是鸡腿和蔓越橘[总统赦免火鸡仪式]
is Drumstick or Cranberry.
两个名字是
Catherine actually
凯瑟琳亲自起的 对不对啊亲爱的?
personally chose those names, didn't you, honey?
- 嗯 是的 - 没错
- Um, yes, I did. - Yes, she did.
再告诉我点这两只火鸡的情况
Help me get a few more details
我到时可以拿来应付媒体
about these turkeys that I can maybe give the press.
他们今晚回酒店会不会一起去吧台喝点小酒啊?
Like are they gonna hit the minibar tonight at their hotel?
酒店房间我们确实预定了好几天
Well, we booked the hotel for a few nights,
不过庆典之后我就要把这俩家伙直接带到
but I'm taking these guys straight to a petting zoo
弗吉尼亚的小动物园去了
in Virginia after the ceremony.
他们去那安度余生了吧
Oh, they can while away the rest of their peaceful years there.
它们就是养来被吃的 估计过一两年
Well, they were bred to be eaten, so they'll probably collapse
就撑不住自己体重死掉了
from their own weight and die in a year or two, tops.
这结局能修饰得美好一点吗?
Is there a more fun way to say that?
以我被赋予的权力
With the power vested in me,
我在此宣布鸡腿和蔓越橘
I hereby declare Drumstick and Cranberry
赦免于感恩节的餐桌上
pardoned from the Thanksgiving dinner table
以及逃税的惩罚中
and also for tax evasion.
这就行了吧
There we go.
他们想飞走啊
I think they're trying to fly away.
这些鸟可真脏
Ooh, these birds are filthy.
- 丹 - 我怎么还进不去了?
- Dan. - Hey, why have I been greened?
- 你能不能跟那位朋友说一下... - 别激动
- Will you tell our friend over here... - Take it easy.
不过是安全部门的一点小问题
It's just a screwup with the security office.
有人因为蓝色证件蓝色丁丁闹脾气呢[指性欲不满造成的睾丸胀痛]
Someone's got a case of the blue badge blue balls.
我把你分配到汤姆·詹姆斯那边去
I'm gonna assign you to Tom James' office.
自从我们在国会宣战以后他们就有点人手不足了
They're shorthanded since we're duking it out with Congress.
我带他进去 他是个乖宝宝
I'll escort him in. He's harmless.
除非你有个妹妹
Unless you got a sister.
你期待感恩节么 马乔里?
You looking forward to Thanksgiving, Marjorie?
- 当然了 女士 - 你在哪过节呢?
- Oh, yes, ma'am. - Where do you spend the holiday?
- 在马里兰 女士 - 我就是从那来的
- In Maryland, ma'am. - Oh, that's where I'm from.
我知道 女士
I know, ma'am.
行了 告诉国会议员普锐斯
Okay, so tell Congressman Price
我刚赦免了他臭哄哄的火鸡
I just pardoned his stanky-ass turkeys,
所以国会投票的时候
so I'm gonna expect him to wrap up
他最好搞定密苏里代表团 行么?
that Missouri delegation when the House votes, right?
一步好棋 女士
Well played, ma'am.
密苏里是国内最大的火鸡生产州了
Missouri's the largest turkey-producing state in the union.
- 仅次于北卡罗开纳州 在明尼苏达州之前 - 女士
- Second only to Minnesota followed by North Carolina. - Ma'am.
还有阿肯色州
And Arkansas.
也许我可以赦免个安全气囊有缺陷的汽车...
Maybe I can pardon a car with a defective airbag...
这样密歇根就搞定了[指密歇根通用汽车气囊问题]
and we can wrap up Michigan.
实际上密歇根是最大的蓄电池酸液生产州
Michigan is actually the largest producer of battery acid.
能不能来个人
Can somebody reach around
把肯特的电放了?[机器人肯特梗]
the back of Kent's head and power him down?
女士 财政部的最新数据
Oh, ma'am, latest from Treasury
住房开工率下降 失业率上升
is housing starts are down and unemployment's up.
能不能把换一下?
Any chance we can switch those?
我只能把这图倒过来
I'll turn the graphs upside down.
对了 明天还有这周末我都用不着你
Oh, listen, I'm not gonna need you this weekend or tomorrow,
- 你就先放个假 - 好极了
- so you can take that off, okay? - Oh, fantastic.
我和我老公正好邀请他家人过来吃火鸡呢
My husband and I are having his whole family over for turkey.
老公? 你结婚了?
Husband? You're married?
是啊 去年就结了
Yes. Last year.
请了250个人 都不是工作上的朋友
250 people, no one from work.
妈 我能和你说句话么?
Mom, can I have a sec?
- 私下说? - 当然了 亲爱的
- Privately? - Sure, honey.
- 什么事? - 好吧
- What is it? - Okay.
我正要去见爸爸和莫妮卡
Well, I was just gonna go meet Dad and Monica.
想来问问你什么时候到
I was just wondering what time you'll be arriving.
亲爱的 我去不了
Oh, honey, I can't.
可这是外婆去世后的第一个感恩节啊
But it's the first Thanksgiving since Mee-maw's gone.
那是挺值得感恩的
There's a lot to be thankful for.
可是我们要在外婆的房子里吃一顿纪念她啊
But we're doing a whole dinner at her house.
我是说... 好吧 我的房子里
I mean, it... or, well, my house.
么说还是好奇怪
God, it still sounds so weird saying that.
是挺奇怪的
Yeah, it really does.
可是我必须在这啊宝贝
But I have to be here, sweetie pie,
我需要和那些国会议员们打电话
cause I've got to call all of these Congress people.
拉选票 你明白的 妈咪需要拉票啊
Whip the vote. You understand that. Mommy's got to whip.
- 好好抽打 这是什么歌来着? - 退化乐队 [Whip译拉票和鞭打]
- Whip it good. What is that? - Devo.
可是你在哪打电话不都是一样的吗?
Well, can't you make those phone calls from anywhere?
- 不一样 必须在华盛顿才行 - 没错
- Nope, it's got to be Washington. - Right.
让人知道她是从白宫总统办公室
It makes a big difference
打电话来的 效果还是不一样的
to know that she's calling from the Oval.
白宫的来电显示不是短号吗?
But doesn't it just come up as unlisted?
不显示地域只显示202之类的啊
They're like 202 or something?
妈 这儿就是著名的白宫食堂
Mom, so this is the famous White House mess.
- 太好了 小乔纳 - 是啊
- Oh, very nice, Joni. - Yeah, isn't it?
在1951年这里被重新修整过...
So this was renovated in 1951 by...
等我一下
hey, I'll be right back.
马上就回来
Okay, just one second.
这不是柑橘鸡肉沙拉么?
Ooh, is that the mandarin chicken salad?
看着很好吃啊 我能看下你的证件吗?
Looks delicious. Hey, can I see your badge?
我锈迹斑斑的警长证么?
My rusty sheriff's badge?
在你一般去的地方
Oh, I'm sure that showing your
露出菊花绝对让你更受欢迎[指丹很混蛋Asshole]
anus gets you into all your regular social clubs,
不过这里是白宫餐厅 想呆在这
but this is the White House mess and to be in here,
你得有这个蓝色的小宝贝
you got to have one of these blue bad boys.
你干嘛啊 乔纳?
Why are you doing this, Jonah?
你看见那边格罗·弗克利夫兰的照片了吗?
You see the picture of Grover Cleveland?
他眼中的泪水
Is that a tear in his eye
是不是因为规则没有被尊重啊?
because he knows the rules aren't being respected?
我天 操你妈
Oh, Jesus. Fuck you.
不好意思 先生 这边有个闯入者
Excuse me, sir. We have an intruder here.
不 乔纳
No, we don't. You know, Jonah,
我希望你是吸狗屌
I hope you die a horrible death
被噎住惨死的
choking on a red, glistening dog dick.
- 感恩节快乐 瑞安夫人 - 你也是啊
- Have a lovely Thanksgiving, Mrs. Ryan. - Oh, you, too.
- 要是你准备好了我们就走吧 - 干嘛去?
- Well, I'm ready if you are. - For what?
我邀请了理查德和我们一起回去过感恩节
I invited Richard to come back with us for Thanksgiving tomorrow.
老妈 你不能随便邀请我的朋友回去过感恩节
Mom, you don't invite my friends to Thanksgiving dinner.
我才能邀请我的朋友一起过感恩节
I invite my friends to Thanksgiving dinner.
理查德 你愿意来我们家吃感恩节晚餐么?
Richard, would you like to come to Thanksgiving dinner?
感恩节早晨
上午 9:29
早上好啊 感恩节快乐
Morning. Happy Thanksgiving.
- 他们就等我了吧? - 是的
- Are they ready for me? - Yeah.
这个选举对我太残忍了
It's this election has just been brutal on me.
我的眼皮完全像是
My eyelids are seriously
基思·理查兹下垂的蛋蛋一样
starting to look like Keith Richards' ball sack.
瞎说 他求之不得呢
Oh, please. He wishes.
夫人 迈克刚才向媒体发布了消息
Ma'am, Mike just announced to the press
说为了庆祝感恩节白宫对外界闭馆
that we're closing up shop for
同时我们在密切监视
the Thanksgiving holiday and we're monitoring
朝鲜的军事演习 就这些
a North Korean military exercise right now and that's about it.
我滴娘啊 演习这么频繁
God, all that exercising and Glorious Leader
也没见着三胖领导瘦一点儿啊 是吧?
still can't seem to take off a pound, right?
他的拉风发型也在帮倒忙
That haircut's not doing him any favors.
韩国总统要求和您通几分钟电话
The South Korean PM is asking for a few minutes to discuss.
疾控中心又上报了几起关于
And the CDC is reporting a few more cases
受感染家禽导致的沙门氏病菌疫情
of salmonella poisoning linked to contaminated poultry.
告诉韩国总统
Tell the South Korean PM
我下午晚点儿给她回电
I'll give her a call later this afternoon.
- 好的 - 那事之儿 那祝我好运吧
- Right. - After, you know. Wish me luck, though.
- 祝你好运 - 好
- Good luck. - Yeah.
- 总统女士 - 艾伯纳西医生
- Madam President. - Dr. Abernathy.
- 您请坐下 盖瑞 - 艾伯纳西医生
- If you could please have a seat. Gary. - Dr. Abernathy.
- 你来啦 - 我来协助总统
- You're here. - I'm here to assist the president.
我和凯伦能应付得过来
Well, I think that Karen and I can handle this.
我很抱歉 你没事儿吧?
I'm so sorry. How are you?
我没事儿 谢谢
I'm fine, thank you.
我得承认 我有点儿紧张
I'm just a little nervous, I have to confess.
- 一切都会很好 - 好的
- You're gonna be fine. - Yeah.
您不会有问题的 我一般做的手术都
You're gonna be fine, ma'am. In fact, I usually perform
比去眼袋复杂得多
things that are a bit more complicated than a De-bagging.
你是说去眼袋吧?
A De-bagging? Is that what you just said?
我以为你说了去蛋蛋[字面:茶包]
I thought you said tea-bagging.
不不 泡茶是我的专长
No, no, no. That's my department.
他说的是字面意思 他不知道另外的意思[tea-bagging指将阴囊放入他人口中]
He means that literally. He doesn't know what the other thing is.
总而言之 你能不能
Anyway, listen, can you just
再跟我讲解一下这次手术?
talk me through this procedure one more time?
很简单的
It's quite simple. I actually
我不会在你的外部真皮动刀
don't have to make any cuts to the exterior dermis.
是直接从眼皮后方切入
It's all approached internally from behind the eyelid.
可能术后会有肿胀现象
There's gonna be a little swelling
当然也会有点淤青出现
and of course a tiny bit of bruising afterwards.
- 啊 淤青? - 是的 淤青
- Ooh, bruising? - Yes, Gary, bruising.
是皮肤下面的一点点的血块淤积
That's when a little blood collects underneath the skin.
在专业医生眼里这些都不是事儿
It's not a problem for an actual doctor.
这个手术的好处就是
Now, the beauty of this procedure
今天做完 周一你就能恢复了
is that we can do it today and you'll be healed by Monday.
而且我看起来年轻10岁
And I'll look 10 years younger.
年轻十岁你就变婴儿啦
That would make you a baby.
- 够了 - 我们开始吧?
- Okay, it's - Shall we get started?
- 好的 - 盖瑞 不好意思请回避
- Okay. Yeah. - Gary, if you'll please excuse us.
我就坐在那儿我会很乖的
It's very easy for me just to sit right there.
- 我知道了 - 真的很乖哟
- I've got it. - Easy.
官方消息称
Officials are reporting a
白宫西翼
下午 12:16
- 沙门氏病菌爆发... - 你看这个报道没?
- salmonella outbreak... - You seeing this?
沙门氏菌病爆发
4州报告37起感染案例
...已经导致四个州出现37名患者住院治疗
...that has led to 37 hospitalizations in four states.
总统还在为自己的脸做永久PS呢
POTUS is still getting permanently Photoshopped.
得让疾病防控中心的领导站出来控制局面
Let's get the head of the CDC out there, calm everyone down.
也让汤姆·詹姆斯出来 他是瓶人形抗焦虑药 胡扯界大佬
Let's send Tom James out as well. He's a tall drink of Xanax.
生病人群数量是达不到
The number of people taken ill is
统计显著性的量级
orders of magnitude below statistical significance.
人们都不懂非参数统计吗?
Do people not understand basic nonparametric statistics?
也他妈不懂怎么把火鸡烤熟了
Or how to cook a fucking turkey.
先生 您在这儿
Oh, sir, you're here now. Good.
- 本告诉我... - 我们被派遣了
- So Ben told me that apparently... - We're being deployed.
执行 去你妈的冷静点 任务
Operation Calm the Fuck Down.
- 是的 - 进来吧
- Yes. - Come on in.
正想找你呢
Just the guy I wanted to see.
我知道这个号码
Ooh, uh-oh. I know that number.
是西德尼·珀塞尔那个禽兽的
The number of the beast Sidney Purcell.
我不知道为啥他总打我电话
I don't know why he keeps calling me.
他对别烦我这种潜台词的理解能力
His comprehension of the word no
就像是个喝醉酒的大学四分卫的水准
hovers somewhere around drunk college quarterback level.
但是我要怎么帮助您呢?
But anyway, sir, how can I help you?
给你准备了个东西
Got a little something for you.
人事部的卡罗尔欠我个人情
Carol in personnel owed me a favor.
这东西可以把乔纳·瑞安脸上恶心的假笑刷下来了
Oh, this is gonna wipe that crooked smile off Jonah Ryan's face.
我感觉它天生就笑得恶心
I think that's genetic.
伊根你知道吗 我和总统的风格不同
You know, Egan, I work a little differently than the president.
至少在对待下属方面 我可不像个
As far as treating my staff, I try not to act
刚踩到乐高玩具的醉酒老爸
like an alcoholic father who has just stepped on a Lego.
我信奉开明和坦率
I value openness and straight talk.
你现在是詹姆斯团队的一员了
You're part of the James team now.
- 是我圈内的人了 - 我很荣幸
- Part of my inner circle. - I'm honored.
举起你的右手跟我一起宣誓
So raise your right hand and repeat the oath.
我逗你的 走吧
I'm fucking with you. Come on, let's go.
真幽默 先生
That's very good, sir.
- 迈克!迈克! - 这次的沙门氏病菌是流行性的吗?
- Mike! Mike! - Mike, is this a salmonella epidemic?
总统会出面发言吗?
Is the president going to make a statement?
她很快就会出面发言
She will be making a full statement soon--
比你们想的要快 但她得做点准备
sooner than you think, but only when she's ready.
而现在有请出来自疾病防控中心的
Right now, though, I'd like to bring up Dr. Robert Weinberg
罗伯特·温伯格医生 温伯格医生有请
from the Centers for Disease Control. Dr. Weinberg.
- 真糟糕 - 没关系的
- This is not good. - It's fine.
大家都在看球赛 再说只有几例感染
Everybody's watching football. There's only a couple cases.
不 温蒂发飙了
No, Wendy's pissed.
她一个人在家应付她父母我父母 还有她孩子
I left her at home with her folks and my folks plus her kids.
妈的 我都不知道我家里有谁
Shit, I don't even know who's at my house.
我都不知道他们是不是在城里
I don't even know if they're in town.
我不想承认 但是有时候
I hate to admit it, but sometimes
我真怕温蒂
I'm scared of Wendy.
不过她还是胸器动人
She still has a great rack, though.
- 看起来怎么样? - 很不错 总统女士
- What do you think? - Oh, yeah. You did great, ma'am.
- 那就好 - 打扰一下 女士
- Oh, good. - Excuse me, ma'am.
- 你们好啊 - 她是不是美呆了?
- Hi, guys. - Doesn't she look amazing?
我滴妈 你就跟个搞砸了丈夫晚餐的
Jesus, you look like a southern housewife
南方家庭妇女似的[南部家暴梗]
who just burned her husband's dinner.
夫人 沙门氏病菌爆发引起了轩然大波
Ma'am, the salmonella outbreak has mushroomed.
已经超过200人感染
The cases now number over 200.
我的天 你在逗我吗?
Oh, my God. Are you kidding?
- 我要讲话吗? - 不 这可不是个好主意
- Should I make a statement? - Ben: No, that's not a good idea.
您的脸腌好之前还是不要见人了
No one should see you while your face is... marinating.
拜托 她的眼睛刚刚被拿走了十年
Okay, she just had 10 years taken off her eyes.
- 是的 - 我觉得这十年还没走干净
- Yes. - Well, I don't think they left yet.
你就先别出现 好吗? 谨遵医嘱 对吧?
You just stay hidden, okay? Doctor's orders, right?
你问他干嘛? 他又不是医生
What are you asking him for? He's not a doctor.
他都没有啥拿得出手的文聘证书
I mean, he doesn't have any academic qualifications to speak of.
我可是有着康乃尔大学酒店管理
Well, I have a bachelor's degree in hotel management
- 学士学位的人 - 你才没有呢
- from Cornell University. - No, you don't.
或许我们得让副总统去做个声明
Maybe we should ask the vice president to make a statement.
不! 别拿他那张老脸出去丢人了
No! He's the old face of this administration.
- 这才是政府的新面孔 - 美丽的面孔
- This is the new face. - It's a beautiful face.
你懂我...
Well, you know...
那我们去问问道尔吧?
So may we go ahead and ask Doyle?
好吧
All right, fine.
翻起白眼来好疼
It really hurts to roll my eyes.
好 让道尔去
Okay, yes, ask Doyle.
但别告诉他为什么
But don't tell him why.
没事的 没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
请不要天天摸我了
Please don't keep touching me every day.
NBC新闻
历史上第一个感恩节
The first ever Thanksgiving,
参议汤姆·詹姆斯 “感恩节不止是吃火鸡而已”
当时完全没有火鸡
there was actually no turkey at all.
- 知道吗 - 神奇啊
- Did you know that? - Fascinating.
清教徒们 他们吃鹿
The pilgrims, they ate deer
和收割的蔬菜 比如玉米 西葫芦
and harvest vegetables like corn, zucchini.
他们还是会冲爷爷吼[过节亲戚矛盾梗]
They yelled at Grandpa, obviously.
- 当然了 - 真理是永恒的 只是没有火鸡
- Of course. - Some truths are eternal, but no turkey.
- 谢谢 议员 - 不用谢
- Thank you, Senator. - You're welcome.
感恩节快乐 预祝光明节[犹太教节日]快乐
Happy Thanksgiving and early Hanukkah.
好 休息一下马上回来
Yes. We will be right back after this short break.
- 直播结束 - 我喜欢光明节那部分
- And we're clear. - I love the Hanukkah bit.
很好 我急需一杯咖啡
Good. I'm jonesing for a cup of coffee.
我是说可以为此在街角卖身的那种急需
I mean sell my sweet white ass on a street corner jonesing.
可不是吗
Yeah, tell me about it.
当然 好啊
Oh, yeah. Sure, yeah.
还是一份奶 糖和代糖各半
Also one cream, splash of half-and-half, one sugar, one Splenda.
如果不麻烦的话
If that's not too much trouble.
没有 我... 伊常荣幸根你服务[姓伊根 名字笑话]
Not at all. I'm... - Egan to please.
副总统官邸
下午 2:05
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President.
本 我想把你请到桌边坐 但我的妻子
Ben, I would have you to the table, but my wife,
她和我一样特别恨你
she fucking hates you as do I.
我们不得不把火鸡扔垃圾桶里
And we had to throw the turkey in the trash.
所以我来了
That's why I'm here.
我们需要您发表有关沙氏门菌爆发的声明
We need you to make a statement about the salmonella outbreak.
为什么总统不做
Oh, why doesn't the president make it?
她因为牙科手术嘴肿了
Her mouth is swollen from dental surgery.
- 她做不了声明 - 你特么在逗我
- She can't make a statement. - You're fucking kidding me.
为什么没人通知我
Why wasn't I informed?
你知道专门有体制应对这种可能性的吧
You know there's a system in place for this eventuality?
就在第24和第26条修正案之间[25条要求总统无能力时副总统上任]
It falls between the 24th and 26th Amendment.
她没有注射镇静剂 不是丧失行为能力
She hasn't been sedated. She's not incapacitated.
所以没必要启用第25条
So there was no need to invoke the 25th.
好啊 如果她没有丧失行为能力 你就用不着我
Well, if she's not incapacitated, you don't need me.
她不是没有丧失行为能力
She's not not incapacitated.
她只是不是完全有行为能力
She's just not fully capacitated.
你们这帮人
You fucking people.
我说 你把宪法
I mean, you treat the
视作DIY披萨菜单
Constitution like a build-your-own-pizza menu.
先生 您冷静而自信
Sir, you're calm, you're confident,
散发出一种刚愎自用的庄严感
you exude a crotchety gravitas.
我们需要了结这件事
We need to shut this down
就像关掉一所破公立艺术学校一样
like a fucking public school for the arts.
我和总统谈过了
So I've spoken to the president.
她时刻关注着形势
She's up to date with the situation,
我们认为病情已经控制住了
which we think is under control.
- 杰夫? - 您对火鸡末日这个词怎么看
- Yeah, Jeff? - How do you feel about the term Turkeypocalypse?
我认为这是媒体发明的一个术语
I think that's a term invented by the media.
愚蠢
It's idiotic,
但能唬住人多看新闻 对吧
but it scares people into watching more news, right?
- 真是神奇 - 是啊 他做得还不错
- This is amazing. - Yeah, he's doing okay.
不 我收到我们面过的那个代孕妈妈的邮件
No, I got an email from that surrogate we met with.
她同意了 我们可以往她体内塞个孩子了
She's on board. We're putting a baby in her.
天啊 麦克 如果你再不专心工作
Jesus, Mike. I'm gonna put a baby in you
- 我就往你体内塞个孩子 - 抱歉
- if you don't get your head in the game. - Sorry.
- 总统在哪里? - 詹姆斯 帮我个忙
- Where is the president? - James, do me a favor.
下次你做牙根管手术 提醒我
Next time you have a root canal, remind me.
道尔轻描淡写沙门氏菌事件
我会过去缠着你 也逼着你一小时内回到办公桌前
I'll come and pester you to be back at your desk in an hour.
天啊 我还以为他会拉一床屎
Christ, I thought he was gonna shit the bed.
相反 他做了夜床服务 还在枕头上留了一片薄荷
Instead he's doing turndown service and leaving a mint on the pillow.
要知道 那可是
You know, that can be
三星和四星酒店之间的差别
the difference between a three- and a four-star hotel.
好吧 谁第一个
All right, who's up first?
我们有国会议员耶格 来自威斯康星州
We've got Congressman Jaeger. He's from Wisconsin.
有招妓问题的那个?
Is he the one with the prostitute problem?
算了 他们都有这个问题
Oh, never mind. They all have that.
众议院就像卡利古拉的卧室[以荒淫闻名的罗马皇帝]
House is like Caligula's room.
- 好吧 你有.. 那个是5 - 好 我知道了
- Okay, well, you got the-- that's a five. - Yeah, I got it.
- 您好? - 感恩节快乐
- Hello? - Happy Thanksgiving.
我是总统 耶格议员在吗
This is the president calling. Is Congressman Jaeger available?
- 当然 我去叫他 - 谢谢
- Oh, sure. Let me get him. - Thank you.
看到没 总统亲自打电话
See? President calling herself.
那可是相当印象深刻
That's gotta be very impressive.
我会开心死
I would die.
总统女士 您好
Yes, Madam President, hello.
国会代表比尔 耶格家
威斯康星州
耶格议员 你好吗
Congressman Jaeger, how are you?
说实话
Well, to be honest,
我家的节过得很是艰难
the holidays are a little tough on our family.
我妻子和我有些矛盾
My wife and I are trying to work some things out.
妓女
Prostitutes.
我想您一定知道我为什么打电话 议员
So I'm sure that you know why I'm calling, Congressman.
当然 沙氏门菌爆发
Of course. The salmonella outbreak.
女士 您考虑过发表一个声明吗
Ma'am, have you considered making a statement?
我学到危机管理中最重要的一点
If I have learned one thing about crisis management,
就是你需要站出来
it's that you've got to get out there
告诉美国人民
and talk to the American people.
如果他们直接从你口中听得消息
If they hear it from you directly,
你就可以逃脱一切责任
you can get away with just about anything.
妓院比尔在给我建议
Bordello Bill is giving me advice.
也许你可以宣布进入紧急状况
Maybe you should declare a state of emergency.
你能做到吗
Are you able to do that?
我可以 但很可惜 我要走了
Yeah, I am, but unfortunately, I have to run.
我希望你能在下一轮投票中支持我
I hope I can count on your support in the upcoming vote.
感恩节快乐 再见 哦天啊
Happy Thanksgiving. Bye-bye. Oh, my God.
我们还有多少电话要打
How many more of these do we have to do?
我们有国会议员科菲
Okay, we've got Congressman Coffey.
科菲 他的老二又安放何处
Coffey. Where does he stick his dick?
这个是卫生与公共服务部的报告
Here's the statement from Health and Human Services.
嘿 你们知道哪家奢华又超级便宜的旅店吗
Hey, do you guys know a luxurious but super cheap hotel?
知道 菲律宾就有
Yeah, in the Philippines.
报告新增了60例感染病例
Another 60 cases being reported
包括新罕布什尔州的议员哈利·谢尔曼
including New Hampshire Congressman Harry Sherman.
他之前也吃不了火鸡啊 除非你把火鸡放搅拌机里
Jeez, he couldn't eat a turkey unless you put it in a blender
然后用吸管喂他
and fed it to him through a straw.
等等 那些火鸡在宾馆房间里 对吧
Wait, the turkeys have a hotel room, right?
对 我们最好去看看咱的大熊猫
Yes. We better go see the black-eyed pea.
- 喂? - 大新闻 亲爱的
- Hello? - Big news, babe.
咱的代孕同意了
Our surrogate Debralee is a go.
赞美耶稣! 你不是逗我吧
Praise Jesus! Are you kidding me?
我们要庆祝 下午来一发
We got to celebrate. Afternoon quickie.
在哪? 地下室?
Where? In the basement?
这次不了 大迈克准备了惊喜
Not this time. Big Mike has a surprise.
我在威拉德酒店定了个套间
I got us a suite at the Willard.
我信息发给你 不 我会用性感信息发给你房间号
I'll text you the no, I'll sext you the room number.
谢尔曼有什么新消息吗?
Any news on Sherman?
CNN和Fox新闻台都说他至关重要
CNN and Fox both say he's critical,
Fox是用一个金发大波的主播说的[Fox性别歧视梗]
but Fox says it with blonder hair and bigger tits.
这是什么? 是线头吗?
What is this? Is that lint?
- 你有那种 - 有 线头刷 给你
- You got one of those—- - Yeah, lint brush. Sure, right here.
太棒了
That is amazing.
能麻烦你给我再一杯咖啡吗?
Can I trouble you for another cup of coffee?
- 我都冒烟了 - 没问题
- I'm running on fumes. - I'm your man.
一份奶油
And one cream.
一半一半的比例
Splash of half-and-half.
一份糖  和一份蔗糖
One sugar and one Splenda.
我日
Fuck me.
是的 议员
Yes, Congressman,
副总统确实是...
the vice president is certainly the...
千年一遇
the president that never was.
不好意思?
You know what, actually?
我等一下回给你 议员
I'm gonna have to call you back, Congressman.
非常感谢 感恩节快乐 怎么了?
Thank you so much. Happy Thanksgiving. Yes. What?
- 谢尔曼去世了
- Sherman's dead.
噢! 天呐 好疼
Ow! Oh, my God, that hurts so much.
- 请不要再这样惊吓我了 - 我们刚刚听说
- Please don't surprise me like that again. - We just got word.
他就不能等到这周末结束吗?
Why couldn't he have waited until after the weekend?
某种程度上
Well, in many ways,
这也可能是个绝好的事
this could be the best thing that could happen.
- 你说什么? - 我们刚刚失去了院里资历最老的一位
- Say what, now? - We just lost the oldest member of the House
我们的总统得顶个纸袋子
and our president can't make
在头上才能露面
a statement without a paper bag on her head.
你没有看到大局 谢尔曼是奥布莱恩的死党
You're missing the big picture. Sherman was an O'Brien diehard.
可能奥布莱恩就少了一票 意味着我们可能多了一票
That's one less vote for O'Brien and possibly one vote for us
如果顶替他的特殊选举及时 对我们有利的人上台的话
if they can hold a special election in time.
新罕布什尔州或许可以成就总统之位
New Hampshire could give us the presidency.
如果早知道 我自己就把他杀了
If I had known that, I would have killed him myself.
乔纳的叔叔杰夫正在飞过来
Jonah's Uncle Jeff is flying down.
他仍然是新罕布什尔州的能够左右候选人选择的权威人物
He's still the kingmaker in New Hampshire.
- 天呐 他是那么 小小的人 对吧? - 对
- God, he is such, like, a little man, isn't he? - He is.
- 日! - 怎么了?
- Fuck! -What?
奥布莱恩正在慰问寡妇
O'Brien is offering condolences to the widow.
我们必须找人就谢尔曼的事说点什么了
We got to get somebody to say something about Sherman.
绝对不能是道尔 谁都行就是不能是副总统
Not Doyle. Anyone but the veep.
- 我们要弄死道尔 - 我不能保证
- We got to lance that Doyle. - No promises, ma'am.
- 什么? - 不保证
- What? - No promises.
拜托
Come on.
- 这是什么? - 你的感恩节大餐
- What is that? - It's your Thanksgiving meal.
为什么准备了两位?
Why are there two place settings?
你知道查理不会来的吧?
You know Charlie's not coming, right?
我知道 这只是为了
I do. That was just for
以防你想有人陪同
in case you wanted someone to sit with you.
不为了吃饭 只为了谈心
Not to eat, just to talk.
或者安安静静的
Or be quiet.
- 我不饿 - 我也是
- I'm not hungry. - Me neither.
- 你又来? - 谢尔曼去世了
- You again? - Sherman's dead.
我们需要你做另一个声明
We need you to make another statement.
本 牙科手术到底是什么的代号?
What is dental surgery code for anyway, Ben?
难道是漂白菊花之类的?
I mean, is it like anal bleaching?
因为如果是的话 你就直接说出来好了
Because if it is, you should just come out and say that
因为美国人民 他们慢慢就会接受了
because the American people, they'll accept it in time.
老实讲 先生 她看起来并不好
To be honest with you, sir, she's not looking real good.
我也老实讲
And I'll be honest with you.
我并不觉得你有对我老实
I don't think you're being honest about being honest.
所以你知道吗? 我要见总统
So you know what? I want to see the president.
- 这就没必要了吧 - 别传话了
- That won't be necessary. - No more messengers, Ben.
如果她想我做她的屁事
If she wants me to do her bullshit,
她可以带着她闪亮亮的菊花来亲自说服我
she can tell me out of her own shining white asshole.
今天的媒体拜访可是个壮举
Today's media-go-round was a tour De force.
更像是对事件的壮费
More like a waste De time.
可能你觉得我忙于
Well, maybe you thought I was too busy
整理你的垃圾邮件而没有意识到
sorting through your junk mail folder to realize
你提到的关于绿皮西葫芦和大西洋城 还有辉瑞[美国制药公司]
you mentioned things like zucchini and Atlantic City and Pfizer,
所有的客户 当然
all clients, of course,
还有"为什么老是打电话给我”的西德尼·珀塞尔
of Sidney "Why is That Guy Calling Me" Purcell.
我还说了其他的单词
I used a lot of other words, too.
我很确定我说了"小" 和 "心"
I'm pretty sure I said "Be" And also "Careful."
我不知道你的终极大招是什么 但我想加入
I don't know what your endgame is, but I want in.
我会把人类的耳朵当做战利品带回来给你做项链
I will bring you back human ears for a necklace.
我是你的
I am your guy.
你是不是有过一次 精神崩溃?
Didn't you have, like, a nervous breakdown?
- 你有过一次精神崩溃 对吧? - 那不是精神崩溃
- You had a nervous breakdown, right? - It was not a breakdown.
更像是一次心理上的消化不良
It was just more a little bit of psychological indigestion.
你刚从内华达回来 而且你输了重新投票
You just got back from Nevada and you lost the recount.
压力一定很大吧
It's got to be a pretty stressful time.
给我感觉你在混吃等死
Seems to me like you're spinning out.
至少我会这么告诉大家
At least that's what I'm gonna have to tell everyone.
真是耻辱啊
Which would be a shame.
你说得对 我都不知道我们在说些什么
You're right. I don't even know what we were talking about.
我们在说你的精神状况  丹
We're talking about your mental state, Dan.
你的嘴唇看起来很干
Your lips are looking a little dry.
- 我看看我有没有带润唇膏 - 乖乖啊
- I just want to see if I have that balm. - Oh, goodie.
本正在把副总统道尔带过来
Ben is bringing over Vice President Doyle.
他坚持要见你
He insisted on seeing you.
原谅我 但你一定要对他客气点
Forgive me, but you have to be nice to him.
什么? 我知道啊
What? I know that.
为什么每个人都在说我要客气点?
Why is everybody always telling me to be nice?
好吧? 这是... 里
All right? It is... oh, here.
- 上帝的二舅老爷啊 - 安德鲁
- Jesus Horatio Christ. - Andrew.
无需多言 我不是做了牙根管手术
Needless to say, I did not have root canal.
谢了 大家 我可以了 请坐
Thanks, guys. I got it. Come, sit down, please.
你都不知道我有多感谢你
Can I just say how much I appreciate
在感恩节抽空来见我?
your coming down on your Thanksgiving
谢谢你
and giving it up to come here? Thank you.
谢尔曼可能不是一派人
Sherman may have been from the other side of the aisle,
但他是一个好人
but he's a decent guy
尽管他还用有色人种这种词
even though he still used the word coloreds.
人无完人嘛
Oh, well, nobody's perfect, right?
你可以省了废话了 塞琳娜
You can cut the shit, Selina.
我已经有两个月基本没见到你了
I have barely seen you for two months.
- 很抱歉 - 好
- Well, apologies about that. - Okay.
听着 我会出去带着标准的迷人微笑
Listen, I will go out there with my golden boy smile,
- 让他们感受到道尔的绚烂之光 -好的
- give 'em the Doyle dazzle. - Okay.
但我想要一些回报
But there's something I want in return.
我想你考虑我作为国务卿
I want to be considered for Secretary of State.
那个位子是我一直想要的
It's the job I've always wanted.
休斯说过如果他第二期赢了就会把那个位子给我
Hughes said that he would give it to me if he won a second term.
他还说了他会把你赶下台
And he also said he'd kick you off the ticket.
道尔的绚烂之光出来了 真迷人啊
See, there's that Doyle dazzle and I'm a big fan of it.
安德鲁 我是个守信的人
Andrew, I'm a woman of my word
我向你保证
and you have my word.
好吧
Fair enough.
- 好的 很好 - 你是被本打的吗?
- Okay, good. All right. - Say, did Ben do this to you?
我可以送你去个家暴庇护所
Because I can get you to a shelter.
- 太逗啦 - 说真的 我知道他说过爱你
- That's so funny. - Seriously, I know he says he loves you,
但你要是不提起诉讼的话 总有一天他会杀了你的
but if you don't press charges, he's gonna kill you someday.
这个我喜欢 和家暴有关的笑话 正好戳我笑点
I love it. Domestic abuse jokes. They just tickle me.
你们大部分人都已经知道了
As most of you already know,
议员哈利·谢尔曼
Congressman Harry Sherman passed away today
国会代表哈利 谢尔曼逝世 享年89岁
今天在他所热爱的新罕布什尔州
in a hospital near his home
于家附近的医院里辞世
in his beloved state of New Hampshire.
我要告诉你们一个消息 一个重大消息
Hey, I've got something for you guys, something big.
我觉得汤姆和西德尼·珀塞尔之间有问题
I think Tom is up to something with Sidney Purcell.
什么?
Up to what?
他今天在每个节目里
At each of today's programs,
都提到了一位珀塞尔的客户
he mentioned one of Purcell's clients.
比如西葫芦 辉瑞公司 养殖三文鱼
I mean, zucchini, Pfizer, farmed salmon.
- 他可没那么蠢 - 很明显就能看出来
- Tom is not that stupid. - There's a clear pattern.
我注意到了 所以我拿证据和他对峙
And I noticed it, so I confronted him with the evidence.
- 然后呢? - 他说我疯了
- And? - And he said that I was crazy.
- 你知道真相可能是什么吗? - 什么?
- You know what it could be? - What?
你他妈真的疯了
That you are fucking crazy.
你当时在选举中口吐白沫
You were foaming at the mouth during the election.
汤姆·詹姆斯
Tom James.
我当时恐慌发作啊
It was a fucking panic attack.
汤姆·詹姆斯
Tom James.
该死的我恐慌发作了
Goddamn panic attack.
你知道是恐慌发作的症状
You know it was a fucking panic attack.
干得漂亮
Well done.
华盛顿特区 威拉德酒店
麦克林托克夫人 祝贺你
Congratulations, Mrs. McLintock.
宝贝 锅里在炖着鸡杂
Listen, baby, I have some giblets simmering
还有五个嗷嗷待哺的人等着我
and five really hungry people,
你得速度快点啦
so I'm gonna need you to be really quick.
没问题 我可是华盛顿特区第一的快枪手
No problem. Fastest gun in DC.
你闻到什么味了吗?
Do you smell something?
并没有 只闻到浪漫的气息
No, nothing. Just the whiff of romance.
不是 我闻见了点味
No, I smell something.
你什么都没闻到?
You don't smell anything?
艾米父母家
下午 6:33
那个汤姆·詹姆斯是什么样的人?
So what is this Tom James guy like?
- 个子高吗? - 我还是去工作吧
- Is he tall? - I should get back to work.
- 总统需要我 - 你才刚到这儿啊
- The president needs me. - Well, you just got here.
你们不和我说说维加斯的事儿吗? 你们找到乐子了吗?
Why don't you tell me about Vegas? Did you two girls have fun?
有一个找到了
Well, one of us did,
但是在拉斯维加斯发生的事就留在拉斯维加斯吧
but what happens in Vegas stays in Vegas.
上帝啊 我再说最后一遍 那不是在拉斯维加斯发生的
Jesus, for the final time, it was not Vegas!
艾米 请别在孩子面前那么赌咒
Amy, please don't swear like that in front of the kids.
我去开门
I'll get it.
别逼我打电话给你们爸爸
Do not make me call your fathers.
搞什么鬼? 你怎么不接电话?
What the fuck? You're not answering your phone?
- 我家人把电话藏起来了- 听着 我得征求下你的意见
- My family hid it. - Look, I've got to run something by you.
我举双手赞成你像个丑陋的妇女一样生活
I fully support your decision to live as an ugly woman.
- 亲爱的 是谁啊? - 丹
- Who's there, honey? - Just Dan.
快请他进来
Oh, good. Bring him in.
- 今天感恩节呢 - 请别逼我进去
- It's Thanksgiving. - Please don't make me.
杰夫·凯恩会面
白宫罗斯福厅
我和州长通过话
I spoke to the governor.
在圣诞节前
New Hampshire is gonna hold a special election
新罕布什尔州要为谢尔曼的席位进行选举
for the seat before Christmas.
- 但是... - 听着真他妈像个巨大的转折
- But... - Sounds like a big goddamn but.
是啊 这是个和丰满且强健的小威廉姆斯屁股一样巨大的转折
Oh, yeah, this is a giant, juicy, muscular Serena Williams but.
谢尔曼的遗孀将宣布
Sherman's widow is about to announce
她要竞选那个席位
that she is running for the seat.
我不断的做着
I have recurring nightmares
和寡妇们竞选的噩梦
about running against widows.
这儿有经审查的名单
We've got a list of vetted names here.
为什么不把它直接给我呢?
Great, why don't you send them right over to me?
- 我正好要没厕纸用了 - 你说什么?
- I'm running low on toilet paper. - Excuse me?
大胡子 你没资格给我名单 是我给你名单
You don't give me names, Beardo. I give you names.
所以拿着你的名单
So take your list, roll it up real tiny,
把它卷成一团绑在信鸽的腿上
attach it to the leg of a carrier pigeon,
让它飞得远远的
and have it fly up tubby's dick.
那么你选谁?
So who's your choice?
我推荐我侄子以斯拉
You know I'm grooming my nephew Ezra.
久闻其名
Heard a lot of great things about Ezra.
杰出 帅气 妻子肯定有八分
Brilliant, handsome, wife's a solid eight.
有了孩子以后 估计也有七分
After kids, probably still be a seven.
你听着 总有一天他会当总统的
Mark my words, he will be president someday.
但以斯拉目前正在阿富汗服役呢
But Ezra's currently serving in Afghanistan.
此外 有任何人想战胜那个寡妇的话
Besides, for anyone to beat the widow,
都得做点见不得人的事
they're gonna have to fight dirty
- 我可不在吃饭的地方上大号 - 我也不
- and I don't shit where I eat. - Well, me neither,
自从我妻子逮到我在厕所喝酸奶之后
not since my wife caught me eating yogurt on the crapper.
我们需要个炮灰
We need a real piece of cannon fodder here,
一个愿意牺牲自己的名誉
some spectacular dumbass
冲锋陷阵
willing to charge this machine gun nest,
然后滚到一边去
sacrifice his name and reputation,
让以斯拉可以顺利当选的十足的傻逼
and then fuck off so Ezra can slide right in.
你有傻逼的名单吗?
So do you have a list of spectacular dumbasses?
名单上只有一个名字
There's only one name on it.
在康涅狄格 我和家人
For my family back in Connecticut, we ditched the turkey.
把火鸡切开
That's because I have a special recipe
因为我有制作西葫芦拌三文鱼的独家食谱
for farmed salmon with a side of zucchini.
- 看到没 它们都是客户 - 这意味着什么?
- See? They're both clients. - Well, what does it mean?
- 我不知道 - 他也不知道 他怎么可能知道?
- I don't know. - He doesn't know. Why would he know?
甜点有苹果派和核桃派 你想吃什么?
So for dessert, there's apple and pecan pie. What would you like?
两个我都想尝一点
You know, I would love a little bit of both.
两个你都要 是吗?
Oh, you want both, do you?
- 有何不可吗? - 我来告诉你有何不可 你这个吃屎的好色之徒
- Yeah, why not? - I'll tell you why not, you shit sack Casanova.
你上了我的两个女儿
You have had sex with both of my daughters.
你毫无羞耻之心吗? 等一下
I mean, have you no shame? Wait a minute,
亲爱的 我才发现
sweetie, I just figured it out.
你知道吗? 你是不是还想上我老婆?
You know what it is? You want to fuck my wife, too, don't you?
- 晚安 布鲁克海默的一家人 - 再见 丹
- Good night, Brookheimers. - Bye, Dan.
抱歉
Sorry.
乔纳母亲家中
新罕布什尔州
瑞安夫人 这些感恩节的旧照都是无价之宝
Mrs. Ryan, these old Thanksgiving photos are priceless.
瞧这龅牙
Wow, that is some overbite.
看着跟兔子一样
It's like a wererabbit.
我发育比较早
Well, I was advanced for my age.
四岁恒牙就都长好了
I had all my adult teeth by age four.
我都不晓得那个年纪孩子们还在系皮带
I didn't know children still wore leashes at this age.
- 祝大家感恩节快乐 - 杰夫
- Happy Thanksgiving, everyone. - Okay, Jeff.
我得和你说
I should tell you that
白肉不够分了
there's not enough white meat to go around.
- 我可不想再现79年的惨剧 - 无所谓啦
- I don't want a repeat of 79. - Whatever.
我来这儿是因为 由于谢尔曼去世
Listen, the reason I'm here... now that Sherman is dead,
将会进行特殊选举
there is going to be a special election
来补选席位代表的...
special election back home for the seat and...
你想让我游说战争英雄以斯拉表哥吗?
Oh, you want me to canvass for Cousin Ezra the war hero?
不 我想让你竞选
No, I want you to run.
你想让我来管理他的竞选吗?
You want me to run his campaign?
不 乔纳 我想让你竞选这个席位
No, Jonah, I want you to run for the seat.
小乔纳?
Joni?
指引我并抚养我的上帝呀
Dear Lord who guides me and nourishes me,
我怀着决心与铁腕走上了这条
I set foot on this path that you have laid before me
您指引的道路
with a strong arm and a willing heart
就是为了震撼政坛 阿门
to totally rock this shit. Amen.
乔纳·瑞安记 第五章
The Jonah Ryan story, chapter five.
众议院臣服于他膝下
The House kneels before the fucking J-man.
我要参与国会竞选了!
I'm running for Congress!
天呐 不错呀
Oh, my God, that's great.
真正的国会还是一些想象中的国会?
Actual Congress or some fantasy league Congress?
当然 要想对抗谢尔曼的寡妇
Of course, up against the Widow Sherman,
简直像把你的蛋蛋钉在钢琴上
it's gonna be like climbing Mt. McKinley
然后爬上麦金利山一样困难
with your balls stapled to a piano.
我投她票了 上帝保佑
She's got my vote, bless her heart.
任何挑战都不能阻挡无所不能的乔纳·瑞安
Ain't a challenge been invented Jonah Ryan can't do.
冰桶挑战 这个你就不行
Ice bucket challenge. You backed out of that.
让冰桶挑战玩蛋去吧
Ice bucket challenge can suck my dick.
它确实引起了公众对肌萎缩性侧索硬化症的关注
Well, it did raise a lot of awareness for whatever ALS is.
- 这货是谁? - 理查德·史培雷
- Who is this man? - Richard Splett.
- 史培雷? - 史培雷
- Splett? - Splett.
乔纳 只有一个条件
Yeah, okay. This is just for one term here, Jonah.
你只能算是以斯拉的一个占位的
You're merely acting as a placeholder for Ezra.
只要我进去了就不会出来的
Once I'm in, I'm in.
我在白宫实习过三周时间
I went to the White House on a three-week placement.
我就是个感染源 没人能甩得了乔纳·瑞安
I'm a MRSA infection. You don't get rid of Jonah Ryan.
听我说 我不是问你 我是在告诉你
Listen to me, all right? I'm not asking you, I am telling you.
对 但是如果以斯拉表哥
Yeah, but it's not my fault
最后要给我舔精 变成天使嗓音的亚特·加芬克尔
if Cousin Lezra ends up eating my nut dust
身旁的傻小弟保罗·西蒙[民谣音乐二人团西蒙和加芬克尔]
and becoming the goofy
那也不怪我呀
Paul Simon to my angelic-voiced Art Garfunkel.
- 你能弯下腰听我说几句吗? - 好啊
- Can I talk to you down here just a minute? - Yeah.
听我说 你就是个行走的21三体症
Now listen to me, you walking trisomy.
在新罕布什尔州 我能让避孕套里的狗屎当选议员
I could get dog shit in a condom elected in New Hampshire.
你就是我的傀儡 是我让你这么风光的
You are my puppet. I'd let you dance.
就算到了我决定废掉你 选择扶持以斯拉的那天
And when I stuff you back in the toy box to let Ezra lead,
你也会对我感激涕零
you will be grateful I ever
感谢我曾经让你的榆木脑袋上台过
let your wooden painted face take the stage.
现在 你到底听明白了吗?
Now, do you or do you not understand me?!
- 是的 先生 对不起 - 这才对
- Yes, sir. I'm sorry, sir. - Yeah.
- 杰夫 - 别来烦我
- Jeff. Jeff. - Hey, leave it.
我不想让你对小乔纳大喊大叫
I don't want you screaming at Joni.
祝贺您 先生 我能否有幸成为您的第一个竞选成员呢?
Congratulations, sir. May I be the first to join your campaign?
- 当然 你是总参谋长 - 不 我要用实力获得这个职位
- Absolutely, chief of staff. - Please let me earn it.
还有有个审查过程的
There will be a vetting process.
白宫媒体说明会
下午 8:03
那我现在先回答几个问题
Okay, I'll just take a few questions first,
然后我再把你带上来 好么?
then I'll bring you up again, okay?
- 好 - 那就这样
- All right. - Okay.
等等 如果你在一张火鸡的床上做爱的话
Oh, hey, is it possible to get salmonella
会有可能感染沙门菌吗?
if you were to make love in a turkey's bed?
- 你说什么? - 火鸡当时不在床上
- I'm sorry? - I should add the turkeys were no longer there.
算了 我马上回来
Never mind. I'll be back.
- 迈克! - 您要见我 女士?
- Mike! Mike! Mike! - You wanted to see me, ma'am?
跟新罕布什尔州的拿破仑谈的怎么样了?
How'd it go with the New Hampshire Napoleon?
- 他有很多奇思妙想 - 是吗?
- He's got a lot of ideas. - Yeah? Good.
天呐 你来看看这个
Oh, my God. Would you look at this?
迈克 为什么她不出来讲话?
Mike, why won't she give a statement?
世上有和我年龄相仿的女人此时正在被舔阴
Somewhere in the world there's a woman exactly my age
而我却要留在这里看这种东西
getting her pussy eaten and I'm stuck here watching this.
不行 我一定要出去
God, I've got to get out there.
沙门氏菌危机加剧
中国南海
27小时后
当海军上将博格尔第一次向我说起这次行程的时候
When Admiral Burger first suggested this trip,
我想 放弃与我心爱的女儿凯瑟琳
it seemed like a very small sacrifice
共度传统的感恩节
to forgo a traditional Thanksgiving
只是一次小小的牺牲
with my beloved daughter Catherine
而更重要的事是要到这里
and travel here to be with
与我们勇敢的水手和海军们共度佳节
our brave sailors and Marines.
各位媒体的女士们先生们
And, ladies and gentlemen of the press,
感谢您们的理解
I want to thank you for your understanding
并对这次行程保密
as to the secrecy of this trip
这就是我最近几天为什么不与公众往来的原因
and why I've had to be incommunicado for the last few days.
同事 我想借助这次机会
I also want to take this
向大家介绍从伟大的威斯康星州第一区
opportunity to introduce Congressman Bill Jaeger
远道而来的国会议员比尔·耶格
from the first district in the great state of Wisconsin.
他们都准备好了 女士
They're ready for you, ma'am.
感恩节过得怎么样 马乔里?
How was your Thanksgiving, Marjorie?
- 还不错 女士 - 感恩节你在哪?
- It was nice, ma'am. - Where were you?
- 马里兰州 女士 - 我也是那的
- Maryland, ma'am. - Oh, that's where I'm from.
我知道 女士
I know, ma'am.
好的吧
Okay.
- 什么? - 刚才是什么情况?
- What? - What just happened?
- 我都不能看她 - 没错
- I can't even look at her. - Yeah.
好啦 谁想要一些热乎乎的豆腐火鸡么?
All right, who's ready for some piping hot tofurkey?
- 夹子在哪呢? - 女士
- Where are the tongs? - Ma'am,
我很乐意帮您拿着您的太阳镜
I'll be happy to hold your sunglasses for you.
不不不 我没事
Oh, no, no, I'm good.
这是豆腐火鸡 是用...
That's tofurkey. It's made from...
小麦 蛋白 有机豆腐做的
Wheat, protein, and organic tofu.
- 给你 - 我们要有暴动了
- There you go. - We're gonna have a mutiny.
我们要有暴... 我给你加点肉吧
We're gonna have a mut... let's get some meat on your bones.
我给你加点肉吧
Or we'll put this on your bones.
- 我刚收到本发来的短信 - 好的
- We just got a text from Ben. - Okay.
他说你的行程进行得很好
He said your trip is playing really well.
- 继续激发爱国热情吧 - 棒棒哒
- Keep waving the flag. - Great.
乔纳要竞选新罕布什尔州的国会议员
And Jonah's running for Congress in New Hampshire.
什么?
What?
这是什么鬼?
What is that?
天呐
Oh, my God. Ah!
- 给你 - 谢谢
- Here. - Thank you.
简直操蛋了
Just... shit.
我跟你打赌 这里面差不多有20块玉米棒
I bet you there's about 20 pieces of corn in here.
可能更多 可能有许多玉米棒
Could be more. Probably fit a lot of corn in there.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
这特么都是些什么... 给你
What the fuck is going... here.